# Morgan Nebiosini

A **Product Designer** who's passionate about crafting visually appealing inclusive experiences.

# **Design Projects**

## **Product Designer**

Freelance, May 2021 - Present

Worked closely with stakeholders and developers to translate business and user needs into scalable designs. Lead UX/UI projects by conducting user research, mapping of personas and user journeys, wireframing of design solutions and creating high fidelity clickable prototypes for implementation.

Clients: Mean Street Tattoo, Aura Finance

# **Other Experiences**

## **Makeup Artist**

Freelance, 2018 - 2020

Responsible for applying makeup to aesthetically enhance performers, entertainers, and other individuals for special events such as weddings or dates. Worked independently and with a team.

### **SUBC Facilitator**

Sephora, 2017 - 2020

Coordinated daily classes for clients to learn about makeup and skincare applications. Led team meetings to discuss ideas regarding class and coaching. Provided education training for coworkers. Delivered constructive feedback to peers for consistent development. Utilized proprietary company technology to elevate client experiences.

#### Research Associate

Agency Access, 2015 - 2016

Researched direct marketing services for commercial artists and production companies. Worked with teams to apply research findings to the computer database.

## Miscellaneous

#### Mica

Grassroots Design Fest, March 2021

Worked on cross-functional design team to develop a responsive website for More Than A Shop, a Non-Profit located in Baltimore, MD.

## Roller Derby - SIDR

Graphics Artist & Skater, 2014 - 2017

Worked with a team of volunteer graphic designers to develop flyers. Skated as a member of the home team.

MorganNebiosini.com Morgan.Nebiosini@gmail.com 631-875-2315 Newtonville, MA

## **Education**

## **Design Lab**

Oct 2020 - Oct 2021

#### **UX** Academy

I was accepted into a year-long UX intensive program, working in close collaboration with industry design leaders.

Projects included:

Mobile app

Responsive web design

E-commerce design

Streaming Service app design

### **Treehouse**

Sep 2020

Introduction to HTML & CSS

Digital Literacy Track

#### **School of Visual Arts**

Bachelor of Fine Arts Candidate Illustration & Cartooning

## **Skills**

### Design

Basic HTML & CSS

Information Architecture

Wireframing

Prototyping

Persona Development

Task & User Flows

Visual Design

**Project Coordination** 

Sketching & Illustration

**UI** Design

**UX** Design

Design Systems

**Vector Illustration** 

## **Tools**

Figma

Adobe XD, Illustrator, Photoshop

Framer

Balsamiq

Maze

Whimsical

Notion